texasroadhouse.com 2018-10-03

# Privacy Policy - Steak Restaurant | Texas Roadhouse

Last updated as of March 20, 2014

### About Texas Roadhouse and this Privacy Policy

Texas Roadhouse is an award-winning, full-service restaurant chain featuring hearty, hand-cut steaks, fall-off-the-bone ribs and hot, fresh-baked bread. Our motto is Legendary Food, Legendary Service®. We hope that you enjoy our food and our Website and come back to visit us again soon.

At Texas Roadhouse, we take the privacy and security of your information, particularly any Personal Information (defined below), extremely seriously. We want you to know that we take reasonable precautions to protect the security and privacy of your information. We also want you to know what information we collect, and why and how we will use that information. Finally, we want you to be able to have control over your information so that if you no longer wish to provide us information or want to opt-out of receiving certain communications, you can do that.

This Privacy Policy is for you, and it governs your use of any Website, web page or mobile application operated by or on behalf of Texas Roadhouse (collectively, the “Website”), and applies to Personal Information provided to us. Please read it carefully. By accessing or using our Website and/or providing any Personal Information to us, you agree to the terms and conditions set forth in this Privacy Policy.

  * ### Personal Information We May Collect About You

#### Personal Information

We collect certain information that does or could identify you personally, such as your name, address, ZIP code, phone number, mobile phone number, email, credit card information, date of birth and other personally identifiable information that you choose to provide us with (collectively, “Personal Information”). If you sign up to receive mobile or email messages from us, we will collect and retain, in accordance with this policy, the information you submit.

You may be asked to provide certain Personal Information when you use or access certain features on the Website, including:

    * Completing a “Contact Us” web-form;
    * Opting-in to receive emails via enrolling in the VIP club;
    * Providing mobile marketing messages when requested;
    * Purchasing gift cards and other merchandise;
    * Applying for employment;
    * Participating in sweepstakes, contests or other promotions that allow for entry and/or participation via the Website; and
    * Using the Website in other specified manners.

The decision to provide any Personal Information is voluntary and completely optional; however, if you choose not to provide the requested information, you may not be able to use some or all of the features of our Website. We also may receive Personal Information through the use of various social media platforms, websites and services and/or from other sources.

#### Usage Data & Site Activity

We will collect your physical location by longitude and latitude if you select a service on a mobile device that requests this information, such as the Find Your Roadhouse function. We automatically collect information regarding the actions you take on our Website (“Usage Data”). For example, each time you use our Website, we automatically collect the type of web browser you use, your operating system, your Internet Service Provider, your Internet protocol (“IP”) address, the web pages you view and the time and duration of your visits to our Website. This anonymous information may be associated with Personal Information. We use this information to help us understand how people use our Website and to enhance the services we offer.

  * ### How We Use the Personal Information We Collect

Texas Roadhouse uses your Personal Information for various internal purposes, such as to provide you with better access to our Website, to improve our Website, to notify you of new products or services, to complete your gift card and merchandise purchases, to respond to your inquires, to process and to evaluate your job application, as well as to otherwise maximize your access to our online services and communicate with you about Texas Roadhouse. We may disclose to third parties Usage Data regarding our Website. Your Usage Data may be aggregated with the Usage Data of others and not identify you individually or it may include associated data that does identify you.

Except as expressly provided herein, we do not sell, trade, share or otherwise disclose (in any manner) to third parties _any_ Personal Information obtained through our Website or from third parties without your consent..

#### Service Providers

So that we can focus on what we do best—providing quality, great tasting food—we, from time to time, may establish relationships with other businesses whom we believe, based on investigation and/or reasonable inquiry, to be trustworthy and who have confirmed that their privacy practices are consistent with our exacting requirements (collectively, “Service Providers”). For example, we may contract with Service Providers to provide certain services, such as order processing and fulfillment, payment processing, hosting and maintenance, data storage and management, as well as certain marketing and promotions functions. We only provide our Service Providers with the information necessary for them to perform their services on our behalf.

#### Other Transfers

In the event of a transfer of all or substantially all of Texas Roadhouse’s assets to a third party, we reserve the right to transfer your Personal Information and Usage Data to the third party. You will have the opportunity to opt-out of any such transfer if, in our discretion, the new entity plans to handle your Personal Information in a way that differs materially from this Privacy Policy.

#### Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement

Texas Roadhouse may also disclose Personal Information: (1) to comply with a court order, subpoena, search warrant or other legal process; (2) to comply with legal, regulatory or administrative requirements of any governmental authorities; (3) to protect and to defend Texas Roadhouse, its subsidiaries and affiliates and all of their officers, directors, employees, attorneys, agents, contractors and partners, in connection with any legal action, claim or dispute; (4) to enforce the terms of use of our Website and (5) to prevent imminent physical harm.

#### User Content

Occasionally, Texas Roadhouse posts on our Website stories, comments, letters and/or photographs provided to us by our guests. By submitting a story, comment, photograph, letter or other information to Texas Roadhouse, you are representing that you are authorized to submit such materials to us and that you are authorized to and are granting permission to us to use such materials on our Website. Texas Roadhouse retains the right to archive posts in the future at our discretion.

#### Promotions

If you choose to enter a contest, sweepstakes or promotion, your personal information may be disclosed to third parties in connection with such promotion, including, without limitation, for purposes of posting your entry with attribution or otherwise as permitted in the official rules for the promotion in question, fulfilling your prize or including your name on a winners list. Also, by entering a promotion, we may require you to consent to the use of your personal information or other information, such as name, voice or likeness, in advertising, promotional and marketing materials. In addition, we may offer certain promotional content, such as a sweepstakes, sponsored by or co-branded with a third party, who may obtain the personal information that you submit.

  * ### Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

There is a technology called “cookies” which can be used to provide you with tailored information from a website. A cookie is an element of data that frequently contains an anonymous unique identifier; the data is sent from our Website to your web browser, which may then store it on your system for future use. Cookies are usually account identifiers and user preferences that allow you to speed through the log-in process by automatically providing the data so that you do not have to type it out and tailors your online experience in general, including content and/or advertising that is shown to you on our Website and other websites. Some Texas Roadhouse pages may use cookies so that we may better serve you when you return to our Website and to offer you certain services. Texas Roadhouse also tracks the domains from which our Website is visited and uses that data to analyze for trends and statistics.

You can set your web browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the option to accept or reject it, or to refuse all cookies. You may not be able to conduct some transactions or use some services on our Website if you disable your web browser from accepting cookies. Our systems do not recognize browser “Do Not Track” signals, but some of our Service Providers who utilize cookies and other tracking technologies on our Website enable you to opt out of certain online tracking. For more information about third party cookies and tracking technologies, including information about how to opt out of certain of these technologies, visit one or all of the following:

<http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>  
<http://www.sharethis.com/legal/privacy/#sthash.1GCAknzT.dpbs>  
<https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>.

We also provide you with additional tools to discontinue receiving certain marketing communications from us. If you want to opt-out of receiving such marketing communications, please see the “Opt-Out Procedures” section of this Privacy Policy for more information.

  * ### Security

We work hard to protect the security of your Personal Information by maintaining physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect the confidentiality and security of information transmitted to us, including: (1) keeping our databases and our web servers separate and protecting each with electronic and physical firewalls; and (2) using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology to transmit credit card information between your browser and our web servers. However, please keep in mind that no data transmission over the Internet or other network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect information transmitted on or through our Website, we cannot and do not guarantee the security of any information you transmit on or through our Website, and you do so at your own risk.

  * ### Be Careful When You Share Information with Others

Please remember that when you share information in any other communications with third parties, that information may be passed along or made public by others. This means that anyone with access to such information can potentially use it for any purpose, including sending unsolicited communications.

  * ### Children’s Privacy

Protecting the privacy of children is extremely important to us. Our Website is intended for users who are 18 years old or older. We do not knowingly collect Personal Data from children under the age of 13. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received Personal Information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete such information from our records. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children’s Internet usage and to help enforce our Privacy Policy by instructing their children never to provide Personal Information without parental consent. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided Personal Information to us, please contact us, and we will take appropriate action.

  * ### Site Technologies

Texas Roadhouse does not create nor provide the technologies used to build our Website, and therefore neither recommends nor endorses those technologies. Any information regarding those identified technologies, their capabilities, limitations and/or applications, should be sought directly from their manufacturers.

  * ### Links to Other Materials

If any link is provided or offered on our Website which connects or navigates to a third-party website, it is for the convenience of our Website visitors and as an accommodation to the respective third-party website owner. Texas Roadhouse reserves the right to reject any request for a link to a third-party website and to remove any link for any reason. Websites linked to and from our Website are not necessarily under the control of Texas Roadhouse, and since we do not have control over those third parties we shall have no responsibility or liability whatsoever for the content or privacy practices of any such linked website or for any link or linking program at any time. You access such third-party websites or content at your own risk. You should always refer to the privacy policy of a third-party website before providing any information to the website.

  * ### Sharing Pages With Friends

The Website may offer you the possibility to connect your accounts from third party social media sites, such as Facebook and Twitter, through an application programming interface (API) or other software. By allowing the Website to connect with your accounts on such third party sites, you consent to our accessing the information in those accounts, which information may include personal information. You likewise consent to our publishing on the Website any such information or actions you take on such third party sites. Additionally, you understand that by accessing the Website via your social media account, activity you engage in through the Website may be published on the third party site. It is your choice whether to use any such third party sites, and you understand that in some instances such third party sites may request to access and publish information about you or your friends from Texas Roadhouse.

  * ### Legal Notices

All material on our Website, including, without limitation, all informational text, the design and all “look and feel” layout, photographs, graphics, audio, video, messages, messaging design and functions, files, documents, images and other materials (collectively, the “materials”), whether publicly posted or privately transmitted, as well as all derivative works, are owned by Texas Roadhouse, its affiliates and subsidiaries (collectively, “Texas Roadhouse”) or other third parties that have licensed or otherwise permitted their material to be used by Texas Roadhouse, and are protected by copyright, trademark and other intellectual property laws.

Trademarks, logos, images and service marks (collectively, “marks”) displayed on our Website are the property of either Texas Roadhouse or other third parties. You agree not to display or to use such marks without Texas Roadhouse's prior written permission.

The materials and marks on our Website may not be copied, reproduced, republished, uploaded, posted, transmitted or distributed in any way, including by email or other electronic means. Any modification of the materials or marks, use of the materials or marks on any website or networked computer environment or use of the materials or marks for any purpose other than personal, non-commercial use is a violation of the copyright, trademark and other proprietary rights in the materials and marks and is expressly prohibited.

All rights not expressly granted herein by Texas Roadhouse to you are reserved by Texas Roadhouse and our licensors.

  * ### Opt-Out Procedures

#### Emails

We hope that you value the email messages you’ve requested us to send you. However, if—at any time—you no longer wish to receive such marketing, promotional communications and/or other offers from us, you can “opt out” by [clicking here](http://www.fishbowl.com/clt/txrdh/lp/unjoin/unjoin.htm). In addition, information regarding opt-out procedures is provided in every promotional email we send to you.

#### Mobile Marketing Messages

If you are currently receiving text messages from us, you may tell us to stop sending them by using the opt-out functionality in the next marketing text message you receive. You can also opt-out at any time by texting “STOP” to 68984. After we receive your opt-out, we will send you a final text message to confirm the opt-out.

  * ### Access to Your Personal Information

It is important to keep the information you have provided to us up to date and accurate. To change the email address you have provided to us, please click [here](http://www.fishbowl.com/clt/txrdh/lp/chemail/chemail-login.htm). Other Personal Information provided to us is not currently accessible online. If you believe that any of your Personal Information provided to us is not correct or has changed, please send an email message to [infochange@texasroadhouse.com](mailto:infochange@texasroadhouse.com) explaining the correction or change and provide any relevant confirmation or reference number.

Additionally, you can always contact us via mail and we will update, delete and/or process any other changes to the Personal Information provided; please mail any such requests, postage prepaid, to:

Texas Roadhouse  
c/o Senior Director of Public Relations  
6040 Dutchmans Lane, Suite 400  
Louisville, Kentucky 40205 

  * ### Processing in the United States

Please be aware that your Personal Information and communications may be transferred to and maintained on servers or databases located outside your state, province or country. If you are located outside of the United States, please be advised that we process and store all information in the United States. The laws in the United States may not be as protective of your privacy as those in your location. By using our Website, you agree that the collection, use, transfer and disclosure of your Personal Information and communications will be governed by the applicable laws in the United States.

  * ### Changes to This Privacy Policy

We strive to stay current on changes in data security and privacy practices, as well as on technological developments; some of which may result in changes to the way we collect, store, protect and/or use your information. As a result, we reserve the right to change, modify or amend this Privacy Policy at any time. When the Privacy Policy is changed, modified or amended, we will notify you by posting the revised Privacy Policy on our Website. Any revised Privacy Policy will go into effect on the “last updated” date shown in the revised Privacy Policy. By continuing to use our Website, you consent to the terms and conditions contained in the Privacy Policy effective on the date you most recently accessed the Website. You are encouraged to periodically check the Privacy Policy available at our Website for any updates or changes, as well as to bookmark our Website to check for updates and/or to print-out the Privacy Policy for your records.

  * ### Choice of Law

This Privacy Policy, including all revisions and amendments thereto, is governed by the internal laws of the Commonwealth of Kentucky, without regard to its conflict or choice of law principles which would require application of the laws of another jurisdiction.

  * ### Questions

If you have any questions, comments or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at [privacy@texasroadhouse.com](mailto:privacy@texasroadhouse.com).
